Guide to the Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1870-1962; 1909-1944; Series III; 16.94; 29 boxes
  - Writings of Stephen Vincent Benét
    - "Thanksgiving Day"
      - Draft, essay, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 62, Folder 2132)
      - Draft, essay, typescript carbon, undated (Box 62, Folder 2133)
      - Draft, essay, typescript and typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 62, Folder 2134)
    - "That Awful Mrs. Eaton"
      - Draft, play, typescript, 1924 (Box 62, Folder 2135)
    - "Then"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 62, Folder 2136)
    - "There Is a Tide"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 62, Folder 2137)
    - They Burned the Books
      - Draft, radio play, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 62, Folder 2138)
      - Draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph, corrected, 1942 May 3 (Box 62, Folder 2139)
      - Draft, radio play, "revised," typescript mimeograph, 1942 May 15 (Box 62, Folder 2140)
      - Draft, corrected, with proofreaders' marks and printer's annotations, 1942 (Box 62, Folder 2141)
      - Galley proof, radio play, corrected, 1941 May 26 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3134)
      - Page proof, corrected, with proofreaders' marks and printer's annotations, 1942 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3135)
      - Page proof, 1942 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3136)
    - "Thirty-Five"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 62, Folder 2142)
    - "Thoughts at a Luncheon to Encourage the Arts"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 62, Folder 2143)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 62, Folder 2144)
    - "The Three Fates"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 62, Folder 2145)
    - "The Tiger"
      - Draft, play, typescript, corrected and signed, undated (Box 62, Folder 2146)
    - Tiger Joy: A Book of Poems
      - Galley proof, 1925 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3137)
      - Page proof (incomplete), 1925 (Box 62, Folder 2147)
    - "A Time to Reap"
      - Draft, radio play, typescript carbon, undated (Box 62, Folder 2148)
      - Draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph, corrected and annotated (2 copies), 1942 November 26 (Box 62, Folder 2149)
      - Revised draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph (2 copies), circa 1943 (Box 62, Folder 2150)
    - "To the Dream"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 62, Folder 2151)
    - "To the People of France"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 62, Folder 2152)
    - "To Rosemary, On the Methods By Which She Might Become an Angel"
      - Draft, poem, typescript and typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 62, Folder 2153)
    - "To See or Not To See"
      - Page proof, essay, undated (Box 62, Folder 2154)
    - "Too Early Spring"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 62, Folder 2155)
    - "A Tooth for Paul Revere"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 62, Folder 2156)
      - Draft, radio play, typescript, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 2157)
      - Draft, radio play, typescript carbon, undated (Box 63, Folder 2158)
      - Draft, "revised," radio play, typescript mimeograph, annotated, 1942 April 21 (Box 63, Folder 2159)
      - Draft, "revised," radio play, typescript mimeograph, annotated, 1942 May 6 (Box 63, Folder 2160)
      - Draft, "dress rehearsal," radio play, typescript mimeograph, corrected, 1942 May 11 (Box 63, Folder 2161)
      - Draft, "as broadcast," radio play, typescript mimeograph, 1942 May 14 (Box 63, Folder 2162)
    - "Toward the Future"
      - Draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph, annotated, 1943 (Box 63, Folder 2163)
    - "The Trapeze Performer"
      - Copy, poem, typescript, undated (Box 63, Folder 2164)
    - "The Treasure of Vasco Gomez"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 63, Folder 2165)
    - "A Trip To the South Pole"
      - Draft, story, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 63, Folder 2166)
    - "True Thomas"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, with proofreaders' marks, undated (Box 63, Folder 2167)
    - "Tuesday, November 5th, 1940"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 63, Folder 2168)
    - "The Twelfth Day"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 63, Folder 2169)
    - "The Undefended Border"
      - Draft, radio play, typescript carbon, undated (Box 63, Folder 2170)
      - Draft, radio play, typescript and typescript carbon (4 copies), 1940 (Box 63, Folder 2171)
      - Draft, "revised," radio play, typescript mimeograph, 1940 December (Box 63, Folder 2172)
      - Draft, "dress rehearsal," radio play, typescript mimeograph, 1940 December 18 (Box 63, Folder 2173)
    - "Under Green Trees"
      - Copy, poem, typescript, undated (Box 63, Folder 2174)
    - "The Unfailing"
      - Draft, story, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 63, Folder 2175)
      - Draft, story, typescript and typescript carbon, corrected (2 copies), undated (Box 63, Folder 2176)
    - "United Press"
      - Draft, essay, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 63, Folder 2177)
      - Draft, essay, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 63, Folder 2178)
    - "Unofficial Guide"
      - Draft of guide to Paris, typescript (photocopy), undated (Box 63, Folder 2179)
    - "The Voice of Poland"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 63, Folder 2180)
    - "Wedding Fright"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 63, Folder 2181)
    - Western Star
      - Notes, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 63, Folder 2182-2185)
      - Notes, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 64, Folder 2186-2198)
      - Notes, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 65, Folder 2199-2205)
      - Draft pages, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 65, Folder 2206)
      - Miscellaneous "unfinished" pages, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 65, Folder 2207-2208)
      - Draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 65, Folder 2209)
      - Draft, typescript and typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 65, Folder 2210-2211)
      - Draft, Book I, typescript, corrected, with annotations in an unidentified hand, undated (Box 66, Folder 2212)
      - Draft, Book II, typescript, corrected, with notes in hand of William Rose Benét, undated (Box 66, Folder 2213)
      - Draft, Book II, typescript carbon, undated (Box 66, Folder 2214)
      - Miscellaneous pages, typescript and typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 66, Folder 2215-2216)
      - "Original material for Book One… removed by author," typescript carbon, undated (Box 66, Folder 2217-2218)
      - Page proofs, frontmatter, 1943 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3138)
    - "What's Your Complex?"
      - Draft, story, typescript, undated (Box 66, Folder 2219)
    - "Who Goes?"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected and with autograph manuscript notes, undated (Box 66, Folder 2220)
      - Draft, poem, typescript (2 copies), undated (Box 66, Folder 2221)
    - "Why Not Cheat!"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 66, Folder 2222)
    - " Wickford Point by John P. Marquand"
      - Draft, review, typescript, circa 1939 (Box 66, Folder 2223)
    - "William the Conqueror"
      - Draft, school report, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 66, Folder 2224)
    - A Woman Wrapped in Silence
      - Draft, review, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 66, Folder 2225)
    - "A World Beyond"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 66, Folder 2226)
    - "The World of Robert Nathan"
      - Galley proof, essay, 1937 December 31 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3139)
      - Page proof, essay, 1938 January 19 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3140)
    - "Worms' Epic"
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, with autograph manuscript notes on verso, undated (Box 67, Folder 2227)
      - Draft, poem, typescript (2 copies), undated (Box 67, Folder 2228)
    - "X-Ray"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 67, Folder 2229)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected and annotated, undated (Box 67, Folder 2230)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 67, Folder 2231)
    - "Young Lochinvar"
      - Galley proof, story, 1932 November 12 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3141)
    - "Your Army"
      - Draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph, corrected (3 copies), undated (Box 67, Folder 2232)
      - Draft, radio play, "revised," typescript mimeograph, corrected, 1942 March (Box 67, Folder 2233)
      - Draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph, corrected and annotated (4 copies), [1942 March] (Box 67, Folder 2234)
    - "You've Got To Be Smart: A Satirical Musical Comedy"
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 67, Folder 2235)
      - Miscellaneous pages, typescript carbon, 1935, undated (Box 67, Folder 2236)
    - Unidentified writings
      - Drafts, addresses, typescript and typescript carbon, 1938, undated (Box 67, Folder 2237-2238)
      - Draft, radio play, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 67, Folder 2239)
      - Drafts, poems, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 67, Folder 2240-2241)
      - Drafts, miscellaneous writings, autograph manuscript and typescript, corrected, 1917-1943, undated (Box 68, Folder 2242-2249)
      - Draft removed from miscellaneous writings, 1932 November 11 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3142)
  - Adaptations of Work by Stephen Vincent Benét
    - "American Names"
      - Printed version of musical adaptation by Jane C. Watt, 1947 (Box 68, Folder 2250)
    - "The Bishop's Beggar"
      - Draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph, corrected, 1946 (Box 68, Folder 2251)
    - "Captain Kidd"
      - Printed version of musical adaptation by Gene Bone and Howard Fenton (3 copies), 1948 (Box 68, Folder 2252)
    - "The Devil and Daniel Webster"
      - Draft, [play?] scenario, typescript carbon, undated (Box 68, Folder 2253)
      - Draft, play, typescript, undated (Box 68, Folder 2254)
      - Printed version, radio play, Literary Cavalcade (2 copies), 1949 April (Box 68, Folder 2255)
    - "Hymn To the United Nations: Finale"
      - Copy of text, typescript mimeograph, to musical adapatation by Douglas Moore, 1947 January 30 (Box 68, Folder 2256)
    - "In a Glass of Water Before Retiring"
      - Printed version of musical adaptation by William Bergsma (3 copies), 1947 (Box 68, Folder 2257)
    - "John Brown's Body"
      - Draft, play script, typescript mimeograph, circa 1953 (Box 69, Folder 2258)
    - "Nightmare at Noon"
      - Draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph, 1942 (Box 69, Folder 2259)
      - Draft, screen treatment, typescript carbon, undated (Box 69, Folder 2260)
    - "Now That I Am Clean Again"
      - Printed version of musical adaptation by Gabriel Fontrier, inscribed and signed, 1942 July (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3143)
    - "O'Halloran's Luck"
      - Draft, "revised," musical play script, typescript mimeograph, 1961 February (Box 69, Folder 2261)
    - "They Burned the Books"
      - Draft, German translation of radio play, typescript, corrected and annotated, undated (Box 69, Folder 2262)
    - Tiger Joy
      - Printed version of musical adaptation, excerpts, by Randall Thompson, 1930 (Box 69, Folder 2263)
    - "To the People of France"
      - Draft, French translation of poem, typescript mimeograph, annotated, 1943 December 21 (Box 69, Folder 2264)
    - "Western Star"
      - Draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph, annotated, 1944 March (Box 69, Folder 2265)
      - Draft, "revised," radio play, typescript mimeograph, corrected and signed (3 copies), 1944 March (Box 69, Folder 2266)
      - Draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph, 1944 (Box 69, Folder 2267)
      - Printed version of musical adaptation by Norman Dello Joio (3 copies), 1945 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3144)
  - Writings of Rosemary Benét
    - Individual Titles
      - "1927," poem, draft, typescript, undated (Box 70, Folder 2268)
      - "American Singer Repeats Success," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2269)
      - "Apologia Pro Vita Sua," poem, draft, typescript, undated (Box 70, Folder 2270)
      - "Avatars," drafts, translations of an introduction to an unidentified work by Colette, typescript, corrected, and typescript carbon, undated (Box 70, Folder 2271)
      - "The Beach-Wagon Set," review of Summer Stranger by Louise Field Cooper, printed version, Saturday Review, 1947 March 15 (Box 70, Folder 2272)
      - "Black is 'Chic': Fashion Mourns Lost Frivolity," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2273)
      - "Blondes Win Nine to One in Paris Coiffure Contest," article, printed version (2 copies), undated (Box 70, Folder 2274)
      - "Bon Voyage," poem, draft, typescript, undated (Box 70, Folder 2275)
      - "Cat and Dog Ballad," poem, draft, typescript, undated (Box 70, Folder 2276)
      - "Child Mannequins: Phenomenons of Style and Grace," article, printed version, Ladies' Home Journal, 1929 May (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3145)
      - "Children's Books: The Story Still Counts," essay, printed version, The New Yorker, 1947 December 6 (Box 70, Folder 2277)
      - "The Children's Bookshop," column, printed version, Saturday Review, 1934–1939 (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3146)
      - "Christopher La Farge," essay, printed version, Book-Of-The-Month-Club News (5 copies), 1946 August (Box 70, Folder 2278)
      - "Compatriots in Paris, or Why I Want To Go Back To Second Avenue," draft, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 70, Folder 2279)
      - "Confetti-Like Trimming Seen on Dark Suits," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2280)
      - "Creation, Innovation, [and Invention?]," translation of unidentified text, printed version, Ladies' Home Journal, undated (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3147)
      - "Dark Prevails in Models of Latest Gowns," article, printed version (2 copies), undated (Box 70, Folder 2281)
      - "Dedication To Miss Converse," typescript carbon, undated (Box 70, Folder 2282)
      - "Dr. Bertha Van Hoosen," biographical essay, printed version, The Peoples Choice, undated (Box 70, Folder 2283)
      - "Duvetyn Leads Materials for Winter Modes," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2284)
      - "Elegy for Janes," poem, draft, typescript (3 copies), undated (Box 70, Folder 2285)
      - "Enfants Cordiales," scene, printed version, The New Yorker, 1927 March 5 (Box 70, Folder 2286)
      - "Friday Balls Set Stage for Latest Styles," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2287)
      - "Getting Crowd Together Easy Matter in Paris," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2288)
      - "Godiva To Tom," poem, printed version, 1929 (Box 70, Folder 2289)
      - "Henry and John," letter to the editor, printed version, New York Times Book Review, 1962 January 28 (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3148)
      - "The Infant Jesus of Prague," poem, draft, typescript carbon, undated (Box 70, Folder 2290)
      - "Jenny Infuses Sleeves With Unique Charm," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2291)
      - "Just the Image of…" story, draft, typescript carbon, and printed version, The New Yorker, 1927, undated (Box 70, Folder 2292)
      - "Lady Chester in Suburbia," review of The Semi-Detached House by Emily Eden, printed version, Saturday Review (2 copies), 1948 December 25 (Box 70, Folder 2293)
      - "Lady on the Postage Stamp and Her Man," reviews, printed version, New York Herald Tribune, 1939 November 5 (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3149)
      - "Lament," poem, draft, typescript, undated (Box 70, Folder 2294)
      - "Like Sitting Next to a Witty Lady at Dinner," review of Mrs. Miniver by Jan Struther, printed version, New York Herald Tribune, 1940 July 28 (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3150)
      - "Lincoln's Birthday," essay, draft, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 70, Folder 2295)
      - "Men Will Soon Adopt Corsets Say Designers," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2296)
      - "Milady's Gown Reach Way Down Drecoll Shows," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2297)
      - "Miss Brazeau Scores," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2298)
      - "Nancy Hanks," poem, typescript, and printed versions, 1934-1938, undated (Box 70, Folder 2299)
      - "Order of the Bath," essay, printed version, The New Yorker, 1931 August 15 (Box 70, Folder 2300)
      - "Our Paris Letter," printed versions, Town Country, 1927-1928, undated (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3151)
      - "Paul Poiret Uses Rainbow But Touches it Up a Trifle," article, printed version (2 copies), undated (Box 70, Folder 2301)
      - "Peter Stuyvesant," excerpt from A Book of Americans, Knickerbocker Weekly, 1946 October 7 (Box 70, Folder 2302)
      - "Pity the Poor Mannequin," essay, draft, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 70, Folder 2303)
      - [Reader reports], draft, typescript and typescript carbon, undated (Box 70, Folder 2304)
      - "Romance," story, printed version, The Chicagoan, 1918 February (Box 70, Folder 2305)
      - "Russian Humors," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2306)
      - "Sheath Gowns Still Ruling at Madeleines," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2307)
      - "Simple Lines Feature of New Style Showing," article, pritned version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2308)
      - "Some Charleston Devils," review of Great Mischief by Josephine Pinckney, printed version, Saturday Review (2 copies), 1948 March 27 (Box 70, Folder 2309)
      - "Summer Gowns Make Features of Long Slim Lines," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2310)
      - "Thimble Summer, review, printed version, The Publishers' Weekly, 1939 June 24 (Box 70, Folder 2311)
      - "This Is England, review of One Fine Day by Mollie Panter-Downes, printed version, Saturday Review (2 copies), 1947 November 15 (Box 70, Folder 2312)
      - "To an Unknown Neighbor at the Circus," poem, printed version, The New York Herald Tribune (4 copies), 1935 April 17 (Box 70, Folder 2313)
      - "To Be Vraiment Chic One Must Be Highly Oriental," article, printed version, undated (Box 70, Folder 2314)
      - "To Rent Furnished," essay, printed version, Woman's Day (5 copies), 1947 March (Box 70, Folder 2315-2316)
      - "Twinkle, Twinkle Little Star," essay, draft, typescript, corrected, and printed versions, Vogue, 1931, undated (Box 70, Folder 2317)
      - "A Valentine for Stephen," poem, draft, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 70, Folder 2318)
      - "Vanity! Mere Man Has a Monopoly Say Shop Keepers," article, pritned version, undated (Box 71, Folder 2319)
      - "Wax Figure Lady Thermometer of Fashion's Shifts," article, printed version, undated (Box 71, Folder 2320)
      - "What College Did to Me," essay, printed version, College Humor, 1926 August (Box 71, Folder 2321)
      - "The Wild Cat," poem, draft, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 71, Folder 2322)
      - "Winter Models With Much Fur Are Exhibited," article, printed version, undated (Box 71, Folder 2323)
      - "World's Tiniest Umbrella Seen in Paris Store," article, printed version, undated (Box 71, Folder 2324)
      - Others, undated (Box 71, Folder 2325)
    - Other Writings
      - Book reviews, New York Herald Tribune, 1936-1944, undated (Box 71, Folder 2326-2328)
      - Book reviews, Saturday Review, 1933-1953, undated (Box 71, Folder 2329-2332)
      - Book reviews, unidentified, 1953-1955, undated (Box 71, Folder 2333)
      - Clippings of articles [by Rosemary Benét?], [circa 1920-1921] (Box 71, Folder 2334)
  - Adaptations of Work by Rosemary Benét
    - "Johnny Appleseed"
      - Printed version, lyrics for music by Elie Siegmeister, American Legends, 1947 (Box 71, Folder 2335)
    - "Nancy Hanks"
      - Printed version, lyrics for music by Katherine K. Davis, 1945 (Box 71, Folder 2336)
  - Writings of Others
    - Allen, Hervey
      - The Syllabus of a Novel To Be Called Anthony Adverse, page proof, [1932?] (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3152)
    - Ambler, Lucy Johnston
      - When Tidewater Invaded the Valley, printed version, essay, 1934 October (Box 71, Folder 2337)
    - Bacon, Leonard
      - "An Ode for the Two Hundred and Fiftieth Anniversary of the Founding of Yale College," reprint, 1951 November (Box 71, Folder 2338)
    - Barker, Creighton
      - "Daniel Webster and the Hay-Fever," essay, reprint, 1937 May (Box 71, Folder 2339)
    - Barlow, Samuel L. M. (Samuel Latham Mitchill)
      - "A Gloucester Litany: In Memory of William Rose Benét," poem, printed version, inscribed and signed, 1950 (Box 71, Folder 2340)
    - Benét, James Walker
      - "An Autobiography," draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 71, Folder 2341-2342)
      - "An Autobiography," draft pages, autograph manuscript and typescript carbon, corrected, with annotations by Lawrence Benét, undated (Box 72, Folder 2343)
      - "An Autobiography," draft, typescript carbon, undated (Box 72, Folder 2344)
    - Benét, Laura
      - "For Stephen Vincent Benét," essay, printed version, 1943 August 21 (Box 72, Folder 2345)
      - "Woman To Man," poem, printed version, New York Herald Tribune, [?] November (Box 72, Folder 2346)
    - Benét, Rachel
      - "Autobiography," essay, printed version, The Stove, 1949 May (Box 72, Folder 2347)
      - "Autobiography," essay, printed version, The Atlantic (2 copies), circa 1949 (Box 72, Folder 2348)
      - "Poem," printed version, The Stove, 1947 March (Box 72, Folder 2349)
      - "Poems," drafts, typescript [copies?] and typescript carbon, corrected, 1941-1946, undated (Box 72, Folder 2350)
      - "Song of the Phoenix," poem, printed version, The Atlantic, 1946 June (Box 72, Folder 2351)
      - "Travel," poem, printed version, The Beaver, 1941 May 26 (Box 72, Folder 2352)
      - [Two Poems], printed version, The Stove, 1949 March (Box 72, Folder 2353)
      - "Winter Night," poem, printed version, The Stove, 1948 June (Box 72, Folder 2354)
      - Untitled poem, printed version, The Stove, 1946 May (Box 72, Folder 2355)
    - Benét, Stephanie
      - "Three Snake Pits," review of The Stubborn Wood by Emily Harvin, printed version, Saturday Review, 1948 March 27 (Box 72, Folder 2356)
    - Benét, William Rose
      - "Barnum," poem, printed version, signed, 1928 January (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3153)
      - "Bartholomew Pendred," story, printed version, undated (Box 72, Folder 2357)
      - "The Conning Tower," poem, printed version, New York [?], 1936 March 16 (Box 72, Folder 2358)
      - Letters to the editor, printed version, undated (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3154)
      - "Middle Age, poem, printed version, undated (Box 72, Folder 2359)
      - "My Brother Steve," biographical essay, printed version, Saturday Review, 1941 November 15 (Box 72, Folder 2360)
      - "My Brother Steve," biographical essay, reprint (3 copies), undated (Box 72, Folder 2361)
      - "Queer Birds I Have Known," essay, printed version, The New Yorker, 1928 June 30 (Box 72, Folder 2362)
      - Stephen Vincent Benet, galley proof and page proofs, corrected, 1943 (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3155-3158)
    - Buechner, Frederick
      - "Stephen Vincent Benet," essay, printed version, The Lawrence, 1942 October 2 (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3159)
    - Carpenter, Frederic [Ives?]
      - "Immortality From India," essay, reprint, American Literature, 1929 November (Box 73, Folder 2363)
    - Chubb, Thomas Caldecott
      - "Turkey Gobbler Land," poem, printed version, undated (Box 126 (Oversize), Folder 3160)
    - Clark, Barrett H. (Barrett Harper)
      - "Sidney Howard: A Few Personal Memories," tribute, printed version, 1939 September 2 (Box 73, Folder 2364)
    - Cohen, Marylee Rose
      - "To the 'Benét Boys'," poem, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 73, Folder 2365)
    - Corday, Tanyah